{
    "id": "921e3f9d811846ec902d15b31bee03e5",
    "title": "General Grammar Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "My windows look ……………… the garden.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "upon",
                "out on",
                "in",
                "at"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I have prepared a rough ………………. of the report.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "draft",
                "drought",
                "draught"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "The reward was not commensurate ………………. the work done by us.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "to",
                "by",
                "with"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "I don’t care ………………… the expense I want the party to be a real success.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "about",
                "of",
                "for"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Vinay does not play cricket, and …………….. does Yeshwant.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "either",
                "neither",
                "so",
                "also"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I know you don’t like me. I don’t like you …………………",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "either",
                "neither",
                "so",
                "also"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Neither did she come ………………..",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "she didn't write",
                "nor she wrote",
                "nor did she write"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "Smoking is injurious to health, …………………. you smell bad.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "as well as it makes",
                "it makes",
                "as well as making"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "On the stand there were newspapers and magazines of ……………….. kind.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "all",
                "every",
                "any",
                "whole"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "If the teacher was to walk in now, we ……………… in real trouble.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "will be",
                "would be",
                "would have been"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        }
    ]
}